RISHABH SHARMA

@ webdevrishabh@gmail.com

+91-8109537889

F103 Block F, Vishwas Park, Uttam nagar Newdelhi 110059

in www.linkedin.com/in/webdevrishabh

Objective

I am expert Web Developer and UI Designer with good skills in, Wordpress, HTML5, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Photoshop, Illustrator and XD. from the last few years, I have been focused on developing online stores, wordpress website, redesigning older websites, landing pages, and other cool stuff.

Experience

Inklik

AUGUST 2019 - Present

UI UX Lead

Lead UI UX team for company.

inzin automotive marketplace pvt. Itd

SEPTEMBER 2017 - March 2019

SR. WEB DESIGNER AND DEVELOPER

Lead website designers. Create an average of three minor websites or one major website per month

Designomania

JULY 2015 - OCTOBER 2016

WEB DESIGNER

Lead UI/UX website designer for a fast-paced design firm. Create an average of three minor websites or one major website per month.

Classic Web Designs

AUG. 2014 - APR. 2015

WEB DESIGNER

Handled all web design for 95% of client projects.

Education

PT. SUNDARLAL SHARMA UNIVERSITY

2019

Bachelor of Arts

HEIGHTS INSTITUTE NEW DELHI

2014

Advance Diploma in Web Designing

CGBSE BOARD

2013

Intermediate

Skills

WordPress

UI UX design

HTML5

CSS

Bootstrap

JavaScript

SE0

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator



Personal Details

Date of Birth: 25/12/1995

Nationality : Indian